<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<serieslist>
  <series>
    <name>Silver Bound</name>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <h3 style="text-transform: uppercase; letter-spacing: .1rem; font-weight: 400;">Silver Bound</h3>
      <h4>Series:</h4>
      <p>In the frontiers of space, existence is all you can count on when your body is not your own.</p>
      <p>Space western series featuring Sheriff Guy Trident and the family he's created and made his own.</p>
      ]]>
    </description>
    <readingorder>
      <book>Silver Bound</book>
      <book>Molten Coil</book>
    </readingorder>
  </series>
  <series>
    <name>The Phoenix Cycle</name>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <h3 style="text-transform: uppercase; letter-spacing: .1rem; font-weight: 400;">The Phoenix Cycle:</h3><h4>To find a mate is everything.</h4>
      <p>A phoenix is only half of a whole until mated but a generation is lost to war and duty insists on survival.
      Their numbers dwindling, their world is changed with the introduction of humans and another alien race, the Scoriah.
      </p><p>Will their new allies save their race or hurry it to destruction?
      </p><p>THE PHOENIX CYCLE follows the events of the <a href="series.php?title=Space%20Grit">SPACE GRIT</a> series. It can be read standalone or in order 
      following the events of <a href="book.php?title=Breaking%20the%20Admiral">Breaking the Admiral</a>.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </description>
    <readingorder>
      <book>The Phoenix Warrior</book>
    </readingorder>
  </series>
  <series>
    <name>Space Grit</name>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <h3 style="text-transform: uppercase; letter-spacing: .1rem; font-weight: 400;">Space Grit:</h3><h4>A new species is coming.</h4>
      <p>
        Half-human half-alien, the Bronsons have created a family from the destruction of a long-ago, failed supersoldier experiment.
        Dubbed the Scoriah, they're ignored by the colonial power, Geonate...until the first Scoriah takes a mate.
        With the possibility that the Scoriah might have progeny, the Geonate are no longer content to let them  exist in obscurity.
        Now the Scoriah fight. To exist. And love.
      </p>
      <p>
        The SPACE GRIT series starts with the novel Black Ice Heart.
        Each story in the series is standalone but they do build on one another. Reading in order is recommended but not necessary.
      </p>
      <p><a href="series.php?title=The%20Phoenix%20Cycle">THE PHOENIX CYCLE</a> follows the events of the SPACE GRIT series. It can be read standalone or in order 
      following the events of <a href="book.php?title=Breaking%20the%20Admiral">Breaking the Admiral</a>.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </description>
    <readingorder>
      <book>Black Ice Heart</book>
      <book>Kilt in Space</book>
      <book>Freeker</book>
      <book>Willing Skin</book>
      <book>Killer Mate</book>
      <book>Wellington's Surprise</book>
      <book>Breaking the Admiral</book>
    </readingorder>
  </series>
  <series>
    <name>Cinder Mated</name>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <h3 style="text-transform: uppercase; letter-spacing: .1rem; font-weight: 400;">Cinder Mated:</h3><h4>Mating is the ultimate superpower.</h4>
      <p>
       Para-talents blend into humanity but not without help. The Cinders keep watch and maintain balance of the elemental powers at their disposal. But a rogue group challenges their authority. The only way to face the growing dangers is to give in to desire and join talents with their mates. Stronger together, the Cinders seek their true partners...and claim them.
</p>
      ]]>
    </description>
    <readingorder>
      <book>Desire the Banshee</book>
      <book>Tame the Storm</book>
      <book>Seduce the Flame</book>
    </readingorder>
  </series>
  <series>
    <name>Demons of Florida</name>
    <description>
      <![CDATA[
      <h3 style="text-transform: uppercase; letter-spacing: .1rem; font-weight: 400;">Demons of Florida:</h3><h4>Wolves, Demons, and the in-between</h4>
      <p>The world changed forever when a rift in the universe allowed demons to pour into Florida every summer solstice. They brought hellions. They brought destruction and greed. But demons had already been here, living within the human world along with ...others. Wolf-shifters and half-demons. Now the world knows they're here and everything is about to change. A handful of lovers face down the coming chaos. Keeping the peace has never been so hot.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </description>
    <readingorder>
      <book>Scent of Cin</book>
      <book>Wolf-Bitten</book>
      <book>Demon Branded</book>
    </readingorder>
  </series>
</serieslist>